<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Happiness Blog</title>
    <atom:link href="http://m.eganchen.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <link>http://m.eganchen.com/</link>
    <description>blog</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2015 11:13:56 +0100</pubDate>
    
      <item>
        <title>After-Dinner Stroll</title>
        <link>http://m.eganchen.com/2015/05/31/after-dinner-stroll.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://m.eganchen.com/2015/05/31/after-dinner-stroll.html</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;After dinner today, Mom and I took a stroll around the neighborhood. We were originally going to walk to a family friend’s house, but were ended up looping around my neighborhood instead. It was nice to finally get some cool fresh air.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2015 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Imitation Game</title>
        <link>http://m.eganchen.com/2015/05/30/the-imitation-game.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://m.eganchen.com/2015/05/30/the-imitation-game.html</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This evening my family and I watched &lt;em&gt;The Imitation Game&lt;/em&gt;, a movie about the life of Alan Turing. I really enjoyed the movie - it inspired me to think on a couple of deep questions in terms of my relationships with myself, others, and the world, as all great movies should. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My favorite quote from the movie is this: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Sometimes it is the people who no one imagines anything of, who do the things that no one can imagine.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2015 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Wellesley Commencement 2015</title>
        <link>http://m.eganchen.com/2015/05/29/wellesley-commencement-2015.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://m.eganchen.com/2015/05/29/wellesley-commencement-2015.html</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;A bittersweet day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This morning was sad in that the seniors graduated. This afternoon was sad in that I left Wellesley and won’t be back until next January. Result: I won’t see my best friends for a long long while.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This morning was great in that the seniors graduated. Their accomplishments at Wellesley are all so great, and it’s time for them to go start kicking butt in the real world. Congratulations to them all.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2015 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Silent Dance Party</title>
        <link>http://m.eganchen.com/2015/05/28/silent-dance-party.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://m.eganchen.com/2015/05/28/silent-dance-party.html</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;From 9:00-11:00pm, Whiptails with phones and headphones danced around Wellesley’s campus. The idea was born from a silent dance party that Haley, AJ, and I stumbled upon in the North End of Boston the past summer. This time, I put together the music stream using Radionomy, and we danced. We began in Tower Great Hall and progressed through Tower Courtyard, the Quad, and ended in the Lulu. It was a wonderful last night at Wellesley with some of my best friends on campus - the Whiptails.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2015 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Yume Wo Katare</title>
        <link>http://m.eganchen.com/2015/05/27/yume-wo-katare.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://m.eganchen.com/2015/05/27/yume-wo-katare.html</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;It’s been a while since my last post… I think now’s a good time to get this guys started again. Apologies self. My semester went a little too busily. Now that summer vacation’s around, I plan to get this up and running again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last night, Galen, Haley, Hippo and I ate ramen at a little place in Porter Square called &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.yumewokatare.com/index.html&quot; title=&quot;Yume Wo Katare&quot;&gt;Yume Wo Katare&lt;/a&gt;. Everyone ordered a small ramen, but the portion was still quite sizable. Check it out:
&lt;img src=&quot;/img/2015-05-27/ramen.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ramen&quot; title=&quot;Big bowl of delicous goodness&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well… maybe the portion doesn’t look &lt;em&gt;that&lt;/em&gt; big. Fairly average sized. The food definitely felt big because the bowl of ramen contains all the pork-fatty goodness of Asian cooking that I miss. The food was heavy and deliciously satisfying, hands down the best bowl of ramen that I’ve eaten in the United States because it’s the only bowl of ramen that embraces the fact that fat is delicious. Talk about cultural differences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the end of the meal, everyone receives a rating on how much of the ramen they finished. “Perfect” is finishing all foods and the broth, “Good Job” is finishing the solid foods, “Almost” means most of the solid foods were consumed, and “Next Time” means there’s still a lot of food left over. The group ended with 3 “Good Jobs” and an “Almost”. Imagine if people were graded on the amount they ate in real life… &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The experience of eating at Yume Wo Katare goes beyond devouring a huge bowl of ramen. At the end of the meal, customers also can stand up and share their dreams with everyone in the restaurant. Of our group, only Galen and I wanted to share our dreams. Since Galen’s studying abroad in France next semester, her dream is to be fluent at French. My dream is to find or do something in every day of my life that makes me happy. What I love is that Yume Wo Katare creates a happy little environment where people eat delicious food and think about their dreams - two things I think people don’t do often enough. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, I loved the food and the concept. Further, I’m glad to find a great non-Chinatown spot to eat.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2015 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pomchos &amp; Up</title>
        <link>http://m.eganchen.com/2015/02/07/pomchos-&-up.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://m.eganchen.com/2015/02/07/pomchos-&-up.html</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;After a long day of R troubleshooting, laptop charger searching, and math proof-solving, I visited Pom dining hall to eat the weekly nachos (Pomchos) and guacamole. Of course, I spent a couple of hours sitting there because not only the Whiptails but also the Caz family came to eat, chat, and laugh in the dining hall. In the evening, the Caz family watched the Pixar movie Up. My favorite moment was Anna pointing out that she and the old man share many characteristics (back problems, clumsiness, etc). Overall, I enjoyed a solid Saturday night with friends.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Unexpected Lunch</title>
        <link>http://m.eganchen.com/2015/02/06/unexpected-lunch.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://m.eganchen.com/2015/02/06/unexpected-lunch.html</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;BamBam brought me lunch today. I originally planned to replacing lunch with in-class snacks since I was busy finishing an essay in Pendleton for my sociology class. Instead, I ate a delicious, delivered wrap. I feel fortunate to know someone with such a kind soul as BamBam’s.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Strength in community</title>
        <link>http://m.eganchen.com/2015/02/05/strength-in-community.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://m.eganchen.com/2015/02/05/strength-in-community.html</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The best part of my day was hanging out with Twitch and the Whiptails in Caz basement after dinner. We baked treats and studied together. In light of fellow student An Ton’s passage, I appreciate that friends on campus came together to decompress and to take care of each other.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;RIP An.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Catching Up with Friends</title>
        <link>http://m.eganchen.com/2015/02/04/Catching-Up-With-Friends.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://m.eganchen.com/2015/02/04/Catching-Up-With-Friends.html</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;A couple of great things happened today:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) I talked to Kelly Z. and Emily Ahn during lunch today. The conversations were special because they’re people who I haven’t talked to yet this semester.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) I convinced Cali to go on the Whiptail spring break.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3) Cali and I started emailing each other about the best part of our days. I’m pleased that there’s an element of accountability to the happiness project now. Plus it makes me happy to read about the special parts of Cali’s.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bonding Over Dvorak</title>
        <link>http://m.eganchen.com/2015/02/03/Bonding-Over-Dvorak.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://m.eganchen.com/2015/02/03/Bonding-Over-Dvorak.html</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I found a very nice &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=G3-ZniwXSYY&quot; title=&quot;The Best of Dvorak&quot;&gt;The Best of Dvorak&lt;/a&gt; video last night while I was studying. I like the video because it contains a lot of pieces that I’ve played in high school. I sent it to my brother, who responded by sending me Dvořák’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=k8-wQZUQ99A&quot; title=&quot;Antonín Dvořák -Scherzo Capriccioso, Op. 66&quot;&gt;Scherzo Capriccioso, Op. 66&lt;/a&gt;. Not surprisingly, I loved the Scherzo. I’m pleased that my brother and I bonded over Dvořák.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Super Bowl Sunday</title>
        <link>http://m.eganchen.com/2015/02/02/Super-Bowl-Sunday.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://m.eganchen.com/2015/02/02/Super-Bowl-Sunday.html</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Last night was the Super Bowl: Patriots vs the Seahawks. I wasn’t rooting for any team in particular, but I had a blast watching the game with the Whiptails in Pomeroy living room. This semester’s social chairs Beckham (Maja) and Turf (Cat) set up a projector and ordered pizza and wings from Dominos. The whole setup was quite impressive. Though I wasn’t super invested in the game, watching the Seahawks/Patriots cheering sections was extremely entertaining. Katy Perry’s halftime show was on point: I want one of the shark costumes for Halloween next year. Also, I learned from Allen that the Madden NFL game accurately predicted the score &amp;amp; outcome of the game. Creepy right? &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ringing Bells in the Old North Church</title>
        <link>http://m.eganchen.com/2015/02/01/Ringing-Bells-in-the-Old-North-Church.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://m.eganchen.com/2015/02/01/Ringing-Bells-in-the-Old-North-Church.html</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Yesterday, I spent the morning learning how to ring tower bells with &lt;a href=&quot;http://bellringers.scripts.mit.edu/www/&quot; title=&quot;MIT&#39;s Guild of Bellringers&quot;&gt;MIT’s Guild of Bellringers&lt;/a&gt; at the Old North Church. I found out about this opportunity from Davie after mentioning that I would be in town for the Battlecode wrap-up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Old North Church has 8 tower bells. A bell rings when a bellringer pulls on the ropes hanging from the ceiling. The MIT Bellringers were kind enough to teach everyone (Davie, me, and two MIT grad students) the basic techniques of pulling the ropes. A bellringer must pull the rope twice: the handstroke (pulling down on the fuzzy red and black-striped part of the rope) and the backstroke (pulling down on the end of the rope after it shoots up into the ceiling). Accordingly, the bell strikes twice. I picked up the pulling technique quickly, but the next steps -memorizing the bell rounds and learning to play in time with other people- supposedly take years to master.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/2015-02-01/BellRopes&amp;amp;Window.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Bell Ropes and Window&quot; title=&quot;Bell Ropes and Window&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After lessons, the Bellringers sent the newbies up to the bell room to watch the bells in action while the Bellringers performed some short rounds.
&lt;video width=&quot;800&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; controls=&quot;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;source src=&quot;/img/2015-02-01/OldNorthChurchBells.mp4&quot; type=&quot;video/mp4&quot; /&gt; &amp;lt;/source&amp;gt;
Your browser does not support the video tag.
&lt;/video&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fun fact: The bells in the Old North Church are the originals cast in 1744.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Afterwards, the whole group grabbed lunch from &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ernestosnorthend.com/index.html&quot; title=&quot;Ernesto&#39;s&quot;&gt;Ernesto’s&lt;/a&gt;. The slice of pizza that I received is the largest I’ve ever ordered. I ate the whole thing too. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/2015-02-01/ernestospizza.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ernesto&#39;s Pizza Slice&quot; title=&quot;Ernesto&#39;s Pizza Slice&quot; /&gt;
Note: The slice was cut in half prior to serving, hence the two slices in the picture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This bell ringing experience was truly special: I feel like I discovered one of Boston’s secret treasures. I’m very thankful that I’m taking advantage of the cool things (like this) that MIT’s IAP period has to offer. I’m also thankful that I got to catch up with Davie - we haven’t talked for months besides the time in January when we met by chance in Bldg 10.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Practice of many firsts</title>
        <link>http://m.eganchen.com/2015/01/31/practice-of-many-firsts.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://m.eganchen.com/2015/01/31/practice-of-many-firsts.html</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Yesterday evening, I went to the first Whiptail practice of the semester. It was our first practice in the brand-spanking-new field house in the Keohane Sports Center (KSC). I’m extremely pleased abou the aesthetics of the gym: the gray and blue color scheme and the beautiful basketball court. Most importantly, the Whiptails have more indoor space to run around! Previously, we were trying to squeeze everyone into the upstairs gym, which made doing drills such as “Go to” somewhat frustrating due to limited space and long lines. Despite everyone’s groaning about campus renovations, I think that the field house turned out wonderfully. I’m excited to take advantage of the new facilities. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s nothing more fun than chasing around a frisbee. I’m super glad that I have a team to practice with regularly again. I’m looking forward to all the tournaments and Whiptail bonding for the coming semester.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Happiness Blog Project / America vs Taiwan Podcast</title>
        <link>http://m.eganchen.com/2015/01/29/happiness-blog-project.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://m.eganchen.com/2015/01/29/happiness-blog-project.html</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi everyone! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I recently watched a TED talk called “The happy secret to better work” by Shawn Achor, a researcher about positive psychology. Here’s the video:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/fLJsdqxnZb0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The talk inspired me to take charge of building lasting personal happiness. I’ve decided to start this blog to journal the high points of my day. I will spend a couple minutes per day describing a positive experience over the last 24 hours. Posts are not meant to be tomes, just quick reflections about the best parts of my day. Hopefully, by focusing on my daily highlights, I’ll become better at appreciating the little things in life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For today’s highlight, I found a Mandarin podcast called America vs Taiwan. I’ve regularly spent time searching for a fun Mandarin podcasts to maintain my Chinese skills and to satisfy my nostalgia for hearing a Taiwanese accent. Additionally, the podcast promises to talk with real-life Mandarin, not the formal speak reserved for beginner language learners. Judging from the podcast’s iTunes description, I’ll pick up some explicit slang that my parents (thankfully) don’t say. If you’re curious, the podcast can be downloaded on &lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/america-vs-taiwan/id325438092?mt=2&quot;&gt;iTunes&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hello World</title>
        <link>http://m.eganchen.com/2015/01/23/hello-world.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://m.eganchen.com/2015/01/23/hello-world.html</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello world! This is my first blog post. Hope to be posting more soon!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
